Hello friends, my name is Anil Rajpurohit
and today I am presenting to you
ICICI Lombard's Health
Advantage Apex Plus plan, which is a very good
plan.
I will explain to you what its features and benefits are.
If you look at the main benefits of the policy, you
can avail worldwide air cover.
In this, if you take insurance of Rs. 25 lakhs or
more, then you
can cover hospital expenses worldwide, which
means you can get treatment abroad as well.
You can also avail tele consultation.
Here you can also seek advice from the doctor or medical practice
nurse by talking to him over the phone.
Hospital expenses of 2 months and the subsequent 180 days i.e. 6 months will also be
covered in this. It is
not necessary to be admitted in the hospital for 24 hours for treatment. Treatment can be done by
asking them for treatment, so all these expenses will
also be covered in this. Domestic air
ambulance will also be covered. The amount of
insurance cover you take is up to ₹5000.
You can also avail ambulance expenses up to that amount.
You can also take a roadside
ambulance. If you use an ambulance to go to the hospital by road,
that
is also covered.
You can also take cover for a road ambulance up to 1% off the time limit, that is, up to Rs 10,000.
You get the same amount of insurance cover as the
ambulance. There is also a
worldwide cover. You can also cancel the tally.
Free and post hospital
means,
but in this, you want the items that will be
covered in the policy.
[Music]
Your in-built insurance will increase by 5%.
And if you also get this vaccine,
if you look at the value added services, you
can see that there are ambulance assistant
services as well, you are also
given health assistant services. There is also pharmacy and diagnosis
services. There is tally medicine with the doctor. There is
video consultation
which you get in the video added services policy.
And the price of this zone is that
if you are in zone one or zone two or in the
rest of India,
your premium is decided accordingly.
Talking about Apex Plus plane,
here you can get insurance ranging from Rs 5 lakh to Rs 3 crore.
You can get hospital admission.  If there is any other
category of patients, you can get treatment done in the room for up to 100% time.
[Music] The tax will be paid as per the
insurance you have taken.
You will also get 1%
restoration benefit of this normal ambulance, that is, if I have taken a
policy of 10 lakhs, if it gets cancelled, then I will
get another 1000000 rupees, that is,
restoration will be done. This will be activated
after restoration, whether it is done or not, you will
get guaranteed community bonus. This is a very
good feature. In this, your insurance cover will increase from 20%
after 8 years, whether there is a claim or not,
in many cases you will get this claim, it will go up to
100%. It increases every year by % in between. You will
also get domicile hospitalization if you are
admitted for more than 3 days or in a way,
it can be said that if such a condition arises in the city
where you do not get a bed in the hospital
or if the patient is in such a condition, then it will be
difficult to shift him to another hospital from home. So, the
treatment taken at home is
called Sigre Hospitalization in the dictionary.
You will also get checkup up to ₹10,000 in this policy,
that too will be a cashless benefit. If you get various
surgeries done, then that
too is 50% off your maximum up to ₹10 lakh. You
can also avail this benefit.
After a waiting period of 3 years, if you are
admitted in the hospital for 10 days or more continuously, then
you are also given an additional benefit of ₹20,000 at one go.
Talking more about the Apex plan, air ambulance cover is also given,
this is over and above, that is, if you have taken an
insurance policy of ₹10 lakh and the
ambulance expenses are ₹5 lakh, then that
5 lakh out of your ₹10 lakh will not be minus. You
can get the entire treatment of ₹10 lakh done in the hospital and the ₹5 lakh and the air
ambulance expenses are available separately. You
can also take Wi-Fi cover if your
insurance cover is ₹25 lakh or more, in
which 10% of the premium will be charged
for the ambulance normally.  I have already told you about
Tally Cancel,
I have also told you about Unlimited Wireless Active Home The Treatment
in the Plus Plan till now
and if you see the optional benefit, optional
benefit means in which you wanted to
add it to the policy by taking additional bridal, you can
take maternity benefit,
how much maternity benefit can you take,
you can take up to 10% of your insurance cover,
maximum up to 10 lakh, that is,
if you have a policy of 10 lakh, then you
can take maximum up to ₹1 lakh in the policy
and if you have taken this maternity cover
but you do not make a maternity claim, then
your maternity premium will be waived for the next 3 years,
due to maternity, the one who
grows up for free will be fooled,
newborn baby is also covered in it,
so the maternity cover in it will be
double the amount of maternity, you get cover for the new born baby
as well,
vaccination is also available for the baby, 1% vaccination up to 10000 is
also available in the policy
If you want to add critical illnesses to this plan, you
can do so. You
can take up to 20 critical illnesses and a maximum of Rs 50 lakh.
You have to pay an additional premium for all these options,
which I told you in the beginning. If you
want to take insurance based on inflation, you
can take it,
but you have to pay from your pocket.
If we talk about the waiting period in the Apex plan, if there is
any specific condition, then
you have a waiting period of 2 years. If it is free
existing, then the waiting period is 2 years. For
pre-existing surgery, the initial
waiting period is 3 years. Normally, every policy has 30
days. Accident is covered from the first day. The
initial waiting period for pre-existing
illnesses is 90 days. And there is
no condition for survival benefit. Suppose
you have a critical illness, then there is a
survival period of zero days for that. It does
not mean that many people say
that you have to wait for two months or three months.  You will
get the critical benefit only if you survive. There
is no money here. If the critical analysis is done, like a
heart attack or death occurs, then you will
get the money immediately. I have not closed the survival benefit for that. That is a
good thing, keep it ready. If you see,
I have added all the features here once again.
You can see the definitions of all of them back
here
[Music]